# **Mohamed Safouen Naguez**

Web Developer

Skilled React Developer with a focus on frontend development. Accomplished in crafting interactive, visually engaging web applications using React.js and modern web technologies. Dedicated to efficient coding, optimal user experience, and staying up-to-date with industry innovations.



## **Work Experience**



**Web Developer** 2023

I spearheaded the design and development of a dynamic and user-friendly delivery service website using WordPress. My role involved and maintaining the website, integrating visually appealing layouts with responsive design, and leveraging WordPress tools



Web Developer 2022 - 2023

I designing and developing user-centric interfaces for our E-SIM provider selling platform using React.js, Figma, and Chakra UI to create efficient, engaging, and consistent designs.



**Web Developer** 2021 - 2022

Rent-Car Project JavaScript and jQuery with back4app as back-end Ensure code quality and best practice Manage DataBase with back4app REST API using JS



Senior technician

2011 - 2021

Maintenance of electronic equipment. Installation of computer and telecommunication

Mount the new computers, to realize the technical assemblies.

## Languages

Arabic: Professional working

**English: Professional working** 

French: Professional working

### **Education**

- Web Developement 2021 - Present
- Senior Technician 2008 - 2010
- 2nd Year LMD Math-Info 2005 - 2008
- **Mathematics Bachelor** 2004 - 2005

#### Skills

- React-is
- JavaScript
- HTML 5
- CSS 3
- Chakra Ui
- Tailwind Ui
- Vue Js

#### **Contact Info**



**(** +216-55-33-93-38



mohamedsafouen@gmail.com



mohamed-safouen.github.io/Portofolio